kiplinger.com 2019-04-23

# Privacy Policy

About Kiplinger | [Join Our Reader Panel](https://survey.co1.qualtrics.com/SE/?SID=SV_4Ys3rvjBw6kOVI9)

Kiplinger.com is committed to protecting your privacy. Please read the information below to understand how we use the information we collect from you and your choices in how we manage your information.

We may make content or services from other websites, including our affiliated or cobranded websites, available to you from links located on Kiplinger.com. These other websites are not subject to this Privacy Policy. We recommend that you review the privacy policy at each such website to determine how that site protects your privacy. 

Following are the specifics of how we protect your privacy.

## When You Visit Kiplinger.com

Our server automatically recognizes the IP address of visitors. This information helps us evaluate how our visitors and subscribers use and navigate our websites, including the number and frequency of visitors and subscribers to each Web page, and the length of their visits. Our goal in aggregating and analyzing user data is to improve the site experience for the user and target relevant advertising messaging and content to appropriate interests. 

### Our Policy on "Cookies"

Kiplinger uses cookies and similar technologies when you use our websites and related web pages.

### What are cookies?

Cookies are small text files, which a website may put on your computer or mobile device when you first visit a site or page. The cookie will help our website, or another website, to recognize your device the next time you visit. Web beacons or other similar files can also do the same thing. We use the term "cookies" in this policy to refer to all files that collect information in this way. We only use cookies in accordance with applicable law.

Cookies serve many functions. For example, they help us to remember your login data, authentication data, and other essential information. Cookies also help us to remember nonessential information such as your preferences, analyze how well our website is performing, or recommend content we believe will be most relevant to you.

Certain cookies contain personal data. For example, if you click to "remember me" when logging in, a cookie will store your username. Most cookies won’t collect information that identifies you, and will instead collect more general information such as how users arrive at and use our website, or a user’s general location.

### What sort of cookies and other tracking technologies do we use?

Generally, our cookies and similar tracking technologies perform the following different functions: 

  1. Essential/Required Cookies: These cookies are essential for the core operation of our website and are automatically enabled when you use the website.
  2. Performance Cookies: These cookies help to improve the performance of the website and provide a better user experience. This allows us to provide you with a high quality experience by customizing our website and content to your interests. Performance cookies also help us quickly identify and fix any issues that arise. For example, we use performance cookies to keep track of which pages are most popular, which method of linking between pages is most effective, and to determine why some pages are producing error messages.
  3. Online Behavioral Cookies: These cookies are used by BlueConic, our online engagement software. The BlueConic Services Platform progressively builds an individual customer profile across several channels, from first touch of an anonymous visitor building up to a known customer in a CRM system, with all real-time channel switches and necessary identity transfers and mergers in between. This allows us to dynamically segment these individuals based on their profiles. Then the BlueConic Services Platform serves the most relevant content on our website or initializes online interactions.
  4. Other Tracking Technologies: We and our marketing partners, affiliates, video, analytics or customer support service providers also use beacons, tags, and scripts to analyze trends, administer the website, track users’ movements around the website, and gather demographic information about our user base as a whole. We may receive reports based on the use of these technologies by these companies on an individual and aggregated basis.

## Children’s Privacy

Kiplinger understands and endorses the importance of protecting children’s privacy, especially in an online environment. In particular, Kiplinger’s website is not designed for or directed at children under the age of 18. It is our policy never to knowingly collect or retain personal data about anyone under the age of 18. If Kiplinger obtains any knowledge about personal information that relates to anyone under the age or 18, we will remove those from our systems. 

## When You Fill Out a Feedback Form on Kiplinger.com

When information is provided via feedback forms, we collect all of the information you provide, including your email address and the type of browser being used. This information is not compiled or used for any purpose other than to communicate with you. 

## When You Participate in an Online Survey

We may share survey information about our users with advertisers and business partners. We keep and share only aggregate numbers. For example, we will say x percent of our users are females and y percent males. We do not reveal any personally identifiable information about you. 

## When You Sign Up For Email Updates and Columns

Kiplinger promotions, as well as outside advertising, may appear on email alerts. From time to time, Kiplinger may send you email notifications about new or existing products and services, new website features, special offers, or to otherwise contact you about your experience with our services.

## If You Do Not Wish to Receive Emails From Us

All of our free email alert services and special offer emails include an unsubscribe link at or near the bottom of the email. To unsubscribe, simply follow the link and enter your preferences. You may update your communication preferences by logging in to Kiplinger.com and visiting your "My Profile" page. For more information, please see the contact information at the bottom of this page.

## Third Party Use

We use third parties, called third-party ad servers or ad networks, to deliver ads to you on our behalf. They also may collect and use information that is not personally identifiable about your visits to the Services and other websites in order to present advertisements that may be of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice or to opt out of having this information used by third party ad servers to provide targeted ads, please visit: <http://www.networkadvertising.org/optout_nonppii.asp>.

## When You Click a Link to Another Website

This website contains links to other sites, including advertiser sites, and content partners. These sites are not under our control and are not covered by our Privacy Policy statement. We recommend that you review the privacy policy at each such website to determine how that site protects your privacy. 

## If You Subscribe to a Kiplinger Publication

Kiplinger follows all industry best practices to protect your personal information. If you supply us with your postal address when signing up for any of Kiplinger's publications, you should be aware that from time to time we do make our subscriber list available for rent to carefully screened companies for a onetime use in direct mail solicitations. If you are a subscriber and would rather not receive such solicitations, send your mailing label or contact information to Kiplinger, PO Box 62300, Tampa, FL 33662 and instruct Kiplinger to exclude your name. 

## Policy Modifications

From time to time we may revise this Policy Statement to reflect changes to our information practices. We recommend that you regularly check whether the Privacy Policy statement has been revised. When we make any material change to this Privacy Policy, we will inform you by changing the date on this page noting when the policy was last updated. If we make any material or major change to our Privacy Policy statement we will notify you on our Website. 

## Exceptional Circumstances

In addition to the above circumstance, we may disclose information about you (i) if we are required to do so by law, (ii) in response to legal process, (iii) to law enforcement authorities or other government officials, or (iv) when we believe disclosure is necessary or appropriate to prevent physical harm or financial loss or in connection with an investigation of suspected or actual illegal activity. 

## Applicable Law

This Privacy Policy statement is exclusively governed by the laws of the District of Columbia and the United States of America, without regard to choice or conflict of law rules. Any and all disputes arising under or related to this Privacy Policy statement shall be heard exclusively in a District of Columbia court or United States court located in the District of Columbia. 

## Contact

Queries regarding this Privacy Policy statement, regarding insight into and the accuracy of personal data that you provided us via this Website or requests to have outdated information deleted may be submitted to our Privacy Policy Officer via the following email address [webmaster@kiplinger.com](mailto:webmaster@kiplinger.com). If you do not wish to receive any marketing information from us, you can use that email address to notify us of your wishes. 

The Kiplinger Washington Editors, Inc.  
1100 13th Street NW, Suite 750  
Washington, D.C. 20005  
Telephone: 202.887.6400

July 2017
